day twenty-nine,
TV guys came to do a story with me.
Is it on?
Caio decided to face a kind of daring challenge,
create a deal from scratch with just a real in your pocket.
the reporter bought some troupe,
Listen, he said,
Ah,
can I simulate here to buy some truffles?
I said, no,
that right there bro is bacteria,
hair dirt.
then I go into the polishing process,
which will have gear on that.
then
priority is those rust point you spoke,
no more
Caião,
how much did you get out of that chair there?
man,
Nothing,
zero.
art of war is you invest in strategy,
man,
now the guy liked
which is why I clean his window,
that i make the other chairs
and then of course,
Choose a legal relationship.
bro,
what am i going to do?
uncle?
we start with a resale plan,
we start with a profit margin
twenty-two percent,
but now working,
I'm making my truffle farms there.
today i already passed to the next level which is the cocoa level,
twenty-five percent,
bro,
Trojan horse,
bro.
the crowd speaks,
bro,
why Trojan horse?
car,
because it does the damage you put in the right place,
boom,
I could make a showcase there at the restaurant,
an idea with the girl?
pum,
I already put my truffles to sell there now too
bro,
farmer is doing well,
I will invest more in it
old you are crazy,
I just lost. 10.
if you find something that you can have income,
falls into the lace bro.
stay there jumping from branch to branch
just to show your appreciation.
puts something for you to think
to be able to make money fast
and then you are directing your business plan.
assemble a strategy there quickly
guy who can do it too.
it's on.
that's it bro,
uses the basis of your relationship,
unwinds
and let's go.
Yes, yes!
look,
here it's full of pamphlet to deliver,
now has 1 mount back there
and now you have to distribute it all
then tomorrow Man!